Wow! This is awesome!
All-Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
It's the tournament! The real deal!
It'd kinda be a problem if it weren't.
Yeah! Of course!
My final high school tournament!
I'm so glad we got to participate!
I'm moved to tears!
Captain! I'm going to do my best!
That's the way, Kurashina! Show some spirit!
Why are they so hyper?
Meow...
Why does this have to start in the morning?
We'll have to beg and plead for
your match to be in the afternoon.
Yeah...
There are stalls, too!
Awesome!
Misaki-senpai, Mashiro Udon's
also putting up a stall here.
Meow?!
Yay! Udon for lunch!
Our Famous Flyer Stock
Right...
I'm sorry, flying fish.
But you were delicious!
Mashiro!
Minori?
I'm gonna commentate on the matches today.
Let's have a good time.
Commentate?
This tournament is actually
getting broadcast on TV.
For real?!
But if I appear on TV, I'll end
up becoming everyone's idol!
I won't stand for that!
You're my idol, and mine alone!
Cover her face with a mosaic.
Wh-What the hell?!
So where's it being broadcast?
Shito Channel
Four-Island-Archipelago-Exclusive Cable Channel
On Shito Channel.
Oh...
Just our local cable TV, huh?
Come on, let's go check the draw already.
Episode Five:
"Yeah. Keep Calm and Carry On."
My, hello, everyone.
Satouin-san!
Oh, thanks for all your help during camp.
Long time no see.
Huh? When did you two become friends?
We formed a first-year alliance.
Is your team in good condition, Hinata-kun?
I couldn't say.
We're inexperienced, and a lot of us are
just now making official debuts today.
But if you underestimate
us, you'll pay for it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Guys, come take a look!
Satouin Reiko
Arisaka Mashiro
Takafuji Academy 2nd Year
Kunahama High 1st Year
I'm facing Satouin-san?!
What rotten luck!
Inui Saki
Aoyagi Shion
Kairyou Academy 2nd Year
Kunahama High 3rd Year
I'm taking on Inui Saki, a
second-year from Kairyou Academy.
I've never heard of her before.
Ichinose Rika
Tobisawa Misaki
Takafuji Academy 1st Year
Kunahama High 2nd Year
I've got Ichinose-chan, huh?
Kurashina Asuka
Okoze Arika
Kunahama High 2nd Year
Shitou Suisan 1st Year
And Asuka's opponent is a
first-year from Shitou Suisan.
That's another powerhouse
team, like Takafuji.
So they must be good.
I can't wait!
Carefree as ever, I see.
Wait, Okoze Arika from Shitou Suisan?
It's Mashiro!
So you really did pick up FC.
Figures.
Do you know her, Mashiro-chan?
We've known each other since we were kids.
Oh, hey, Tunarika-chan.
Don't call me that!
If she's the same age as Mashiro-cchi,
that means she won a starting
spot at Shitou Suisan
despite being a first-year.
When I heard Mashiro picked up FC,
I really wanted to play against her.
So I tried my hardest.
We're in different blocks, you know.
That means we can only face
each other in the final.
You'd better make it all the way.
I'll make sure I do as well.
Whoa. You seem confident, Tunarika-chan.
Seriously, stop calling me that!
Just stop! Don't you dare
call me that again!
Dear me, Arika. Yet again, you're forgetting
to address your elders politely.
Lady Mayu?!
As my pupil, your failings are my own.
How you sadden me so.
Forgive me, milady!
I beg of you! Please don't discipline me!
I'm afraid I'll have to.
You meanie...
My dear...
Rest assured.
I love you too much to put you through that.
Milady...
Apparently it's a tradition at Shitou Suisan
for students to exchange vows with
their seniors and learn from them.
"Exchange vows"?
Let's transfer!
Not on your life.
The opening ceremony will begin soon.
All participants are requested
to assemble at the event HQ.
Pardon me for intruding.
We shall see you later.
See ya, Mashiro.
It's the nice girl from back then.
So she plays FC.
U-Um, thank you very much for the—
Saki.
To all our Shito Channel viewers
at home, the wait is over!
I'm Hosaka Minori, first-year at Kunahama
High, and I'm your commentator!
Takafuji Academy
The All-Japan Flying Circus Summer
Tournament West Kyushu Qualifiers are upon us!
I can finally wear a flying suit in a match!
I can't wait!
Settle down, Asuka-senpai.
You're way too hypurr.
You look great in your
suit too, Mashiro-chan!
I wanna stick a plate armor on this.
Why the heck?
It's almost time!
Do your best out there, team.
I'd like to make it to the second
round and face Shindo-san again.
You really are aiming for
the quarterfinals, huh?
I'm going to become the Ruler of the Heavens!
Isn't that...
Business as usual with Asuka, I see.
That's the way, Kurashina!
It's all about spirit!
Yeah!
We'll now hold the first match
of round one in the A Block.
Best of luck, Mashiro-chan.
Calm down.
I really do have the worst luck.
Okay, okay.
I mean, I don't think I stand a
chance in hell against Satouin-san.
Look, you've gotten much better
since the training camp.
Have some confidence in yourself.
How do you want to go about this match?
Forget winning or losing for now.
Playing the way you want to comes first.
I...
I want to take her on
fair-and-square as a speeder!
Got it.
But you have to start the
low yo-yo later than usual.
Why is that?
Satouin-san's an all-rounder type.
More often than not, all-rounders change
their strategy based on their opponent.
But she doesn't know that you've
changed to speeder yet, does she?
Probably not.
If we make her believe
that you're a fighter,
she won't take a shortcut.
And then we can turn it into an all-out race.
I see. Understood.
Assuming you win the first line
sprint by a narrow margin,
you'll have the edge in speed
going into the second line.
You should be able to
take the third buoy, too.
Got it!
It's finally time!
Second-year at the powerhouse Takafuji
Academy and self-proclaimed "Purple Rose,"
Satouin Reiko, takes on
first-year at Kunahama High and
poster girl of Mashiro Udon,
Arisaka Mashiro, in a match that begins now!
On your marks...
Set!
Both players are off and flying!
However, Arisaka seems to
have made a delayed start!
It's all right. Calm down.
Start the low yo-yo!
R-Right!
Satou-kun, your opponent's using a low yo-yo.
Call me Satouin, Captain.
Wait, what? A low yo-yo?
Isn't she a fighter?
Point to Arisaka!
Yes!
Now this is a surprise!
Arisaka, a first-year in her debut match,
has just scored the first point!
Wow!
Go, Mashiro!
Is she a speeder?!
Not to mention she's pretty fast!
Satou-kun, you can't beat her in a race.
Take a shortcut to the third line.
Please, Captain. It's Satouin.
Point to Arisaka!
All right!
Arisaka is up, 2-0!
Awesome!
This is as far as you go.
What do I do?
Oh, right.
Remember the practice with Rika!
All right. Nice decision.
She's completely changed since camp.
She's got her basics down pat.
However!
I'm used to taking on a speeder
who sticks to the basics!
Mashiro-cchi's using her petite frame
to her advantage and hanging in there!
Point to Satouin!
Here comes my counterattack!
I'll leave the rest to you, Satou-kun.
As I've been saying, call me Satouin!
This match is over!
Satouin wins!
Good game.
That was a good game.
Man, I lost after all.
But you were dazzling up
there, like a flying fish!
You did well, Mashiro.
Yeah.
Thank you!
The second match of round one in the B Block:
Kunahama High's Tobisawa Misaki versus
Takafuji Academy's Ichinose Rika.
After Ichinose scored the first point,
the match has taken a one-sided turn.
Point to Tobisawa!
Misaki-chan's so awesome!
She must be the type that
steps it up when it matters!
She's like a cat after a mouse.
A dog after a bone...
Or Madoka when she yells at me.
Hey, I don't yell at you that much.
Rika...
You can't fall back any farther.
O-Okay!
She's fast!
Go, Rika!
Whose side are you on?
Both!
Point to Tobisawa!
Ichinose's trying desperately
to escape this dogfight,
but Tobisawa's completely blocking her path!
I won't lose!
I see now.
What are you talking about?
She's deliberately trying
to make you touch her
so she can use that recoil to make a getaway.
What am I supposed to do?
Keep circling her.
Don't make a move yourself.
Ignore all the bait.
Roger that!
In situations like these, the first one
to make a move is at a disadvantage.
So they're planning to stall
until the final whistle?
I never knew there were
strategies like these.
I'm learning a lot.
This match is over!
Tobisawa wins!
Tobisawa just took out a member
of the mighty Takafuji Academy!
Good game!
Well done, Misaki!
That was amazing!
You're awesome, Misaki-chan!
That will do nicely, I suppose.
Tobisawa-san!
Hm?
Good game!
You were simply better.
Thank you for playing me.
Thank you, too.
Let's play again sometime.
I'll win next time!
I focused so hard in order to find
her openings that I'm exhausted meow.
Well, winning ain't easy.
Yeah...
Tobisawa's all about that confidence, huh?
A tennis player who won the French
Open at just eighteen said,
"Things won't always go
the way you want them to,
so confidence becomes essential."
All right!
I'm gonna go play with all the
confidence in the world, then.
Just try to make sure it's not baseless.
What was that?!
The tenth match of round one will begin shortly.
Participants, please get ready.
You're facing Inui Saki from Kairyou,
but there's zero data on her.
There's no way to tell how she'll play.
Don't worry about it!
If I go fast, faster, fastest, and
leave her in my dust, I'll win!
Speed always reigns supreme!
And it's all about spirit!
Well, whatever.
Um...
I am Irina. Second of Inui Saki.
I'm Hinata.
Nice to meet you.
It is her first match in Japan.
Please be gentle.
So she used to play abroad, then?
Yes, in England.
Well, let's both do our best.
England?
The birthplace of Flying Circus...
I've never seen those Grav-Shoes before.
Captain... Your opponent, Inui,
is short and has a light frame.
She could be an evasive fighter-type.
Pick up your pace on the first line
so you don't get caught in a dogfight.
I know!
On your marks...
Set!
Captain! She's a speeder, too!
She's quick.
So it's an all-out race?
Point to Inui!
The score is 3-0! Can this
deficit be overturned?!
Hinata, I'm having the
time of my life right now!
I have in front of my eyes
someone faster than me.
Then what choice do I have...
but to overtake them with spirit?!
This match is over!
Inui wins!
Bro, you were so fast out there!
I was moved to tears, Captain!
The way you stuck to your
beliefs was wonderful!
She's an incredible speeder.
Oh, that was no big deal.
Uh, it was most definitely a big deal.
Oh, right.
I've been meaning to ask
about those Grav-Shoes.
These are Avalon Grav-Shoes.
My father started the brand.
Avalon...
See you later!
C-C-Coach, it's finally
time for my debut match.
Yeah. Keep calm and carry on.
It's all good!
Right now, I'm totally
a flying fish at heart!
Uh...
Your opponent is a speeder.
To start with, play by the
book and see what she does.
Got it! I'll see what
she does, and then some!
I'm definitely not gonna lose!
Okay!
L-Let's b-both have f-fun!
Now, it's time for another
B Block first-round match:
Kunahama High's flying
fish-lover Kurashina Asuka versus
Shitou Suisan's promising
fine tuna, Okoze Arika!
On your marks...
Set!
Arika, low yo-yo!
Sure!
Oh, Okoze's using a low yo-yo to accelerate!
Asuka, take a shortcut to the second line!
O-Okay!
Point to Okoze!
Here she comes!
Ambushing her at the second line.
Here we go!
What's with those wide scissors?!
But because her movements are so big,
it should be easier to get a read on them.
Take another shortcut!
R-Right!
That was no good at all.
But I can't believe there's
a passing maneuver like that!
That's what makes official
matches so enjoyable.
This is fun!
Huh?
Not knowing what's coming is exciting!
I'll take her down next time!
Point to Okoze!
Shake them up more, Arika.
Yes, milady!
Wait for the big move...
Here it is!
Whoa, way to go.
She's matching Arika move for move!
Right! Left!
What? How can she keep up with me?!
Right... or not?!
A tailspin?!
It can't be!
While in a tailspin...
...she pulled off an air kick turn?
Wow. Talk about a free-spirited brand of FC.
Asuka.
That's the way. Keep the dogfight going.
Okay!
This match is over!
Kurashina wins!
Way to go, Asuka!
You were incredible, Asuka-senpai!
You were a flying fish up there!
She's asleep?!
Wh-Why'd you suddenly fall asleep?!
Watch out! Grab hold of her!
She's surprisingly heavy!
Aw, jeez. I'll carry her to the rest area!
I'm sorry, but I was really
looking forward to today.
And then I started to get nervous,
so I couldn't sleep a wink.
So that's why you were more hyper than usual.
What are we gonna do with you?
Oh, right.
Congrats on your first victory.
Thank you very much!
You'd better get some sleep tonight.
We've got the second round tomorrow.
And she's already asleep.
To Be Continued
Preview
Let's zipzap, Shindou-san.
I'll give it all I've got!
Thanks, Asuka.
Episode Six:
"Is That All You've Got?"
Is that all you've got?